Guide to the Western Connecticut State University Photographs and Miscellanea RG 8
Western Connecticut State University Archives and Special Collections
- Series III: Clippings, 55202
  - 1984, 55619
    - April 1984 Clippings (copies), 55635 (Box clippings_1, Folder 45)
      Apr 5-8, 1984: Ives Center building; April 6, 1984: "Fantasticks" by The Dramatons at WCSU; Apr 6-17, 1984: Several articles on music in the area; Apr 13, 1984: Conference on math and science as women's careers; April 16,21, 1984: WestConn professors near contract agreement; Apr 22, 1984: Coach Ted Hines interviewed; Apr 29,1984: John M. Eichrodt obituary.
    - April 1984 Clippings (copies) - Sports, 55634 (Box clippings_1, Folder 46)
      Apr 8, 1984: Men's and women's baseball; Apri.27,1984; Rajcula comments about Women's Professional Basketball League.
    - May 1984 Clippings (copies), 55633 (Box clippings_1, Folder 47)
      May 1, 1984: T. Clark Hull, State Appellate Court judge, to speak at commencement; May 4: Prof. James Scrimgeour interview; May 8: Cooperative effort of Union Carbide and area educators to promote math and sciencs; May 8: House passes bill authorizing fieldhouse and athletic field; May 9: WestConn new state weather-watcher; May 11: Ronald W. Shaw appointed public safety director at WCSU; May 15, 1984: Ruth Kohl, head of Nursing Department leaves post.
    - May 1984 Clippings (copies) - Sports, 55632 (Box clippings_1, Folder 48)
      May 6, 1984: John Welch, assistant men's basketball coach and trainer, interview.
    - June 1984 Clippings (copies), 55631 (Box clippings_1, Folder 49)
      Jun 1,3, 1984: Weather related articles and Dr. Mel Goldstein; Jun 3: Dorothy Greenwald interview; Jun 14: Gov. O'Neill signs bonding bill for planned; Jun 20: Dr. Peter Siver: Weeds and algae may choke Candlewood lake's future; Jun 21: Candlewood Lake Authority thrust into role of saving lake; Jun 28: Bonnie Yake interview.
    - July 1984 Clippings (copies), 55630 (Box clippings_1, Folder 50)
      Jul 5, 1984: WCSU offers new master's in business of science; Jul 5, 1984: 600 political science books donated to Haas Library by Prudential-Bache Securities; Jul 5,6,19, 1984: Richard H. Sullivan appointed V.P. of Administrative Affairs; Jul 9, 1984: Fred Tesch, Chairman of the Management Department interview; Jul 10, 1984: Letter to the Editor: College library called inadequate; Jul 19, 1984: Ives Center editorial; Jul 25, 1984: Rebuttal to Jul 10 letter to editor.
    - August 1984 Clippings (copies), 55629 (Box clippings_1, Folder 51)
      Aug 5,8,13, 1984: Richard Moryl's "The Golden Phoenix; Aug 5, 1984: Candlewood Playhouse seeks comback; Aug 7, 1984: 11% tuition hike for state; Aug 22,24,25,27, 1984: Padanaram firefighters 100th b/day; Aug 22,31, 1984: WCSU offers two master's degrees in health care undergrads; Aug 24, 1984: WCSU continues its expansion; Aug 26, 1984: Ives memorial takes shape.
    - August 1984 Clippings (copies) - Sports, 55628 (Box clippings_1, Folder 52)
      Aug 26, 1984: WCSU football team seeks consistency.
    - September 1984 Clippings (copies), 55627 (Box clippings_1, Folder 53)
      Sep 5, 1984: NU supports Candlewood Lake weed plan; Sep 12-16, 1984: Tricentennial Celebration; Sep 15, 1984: Dr. Janick and "Project Acorn: The Greening of WestConn;" Sep 16,27,29, 1984: Donald E. Weened and the Charles Ives Center; Sep 19, 1984: Danbury Preservation Trust; Sep 21, 24, 1984: WCSU receives grant for phosphorus study in Candlewood Lake; Sep 23, 1984: Danbury's Music Fair: An Ives Tribute; Sep 24, 1984: Reception launching the Charles Ives Center for the Arts.
    - September 1984 Clippings (copies) - Sports, 55626 (Box clippings_1, Folder 54)
      Sep 29, 1984: Football: Charles Blaszka, Jamie Prunty, and Guy Samuelson featured.
    - October 1984 Clippings (copies), 55625 (Box clippings_1, Folder 55)
      Oct 1,3, 1984: Musical Fair at the Ives Center; Oct 2, 1984: Teacher program revised for state certification; Oct 7, 1984: WestConn has local image problem; Oct 22, 1984: Presidential debate viewed by WCSU students; Oct 28, 1984: Andrea B. O'Connor, new nursing director; Oct 31, 1984: Contracts for design of fieldhouse complex signed.
    - October 1984 Clippings (copies) - Sports, 55624 (Box clippings_1, Folder 56)
      Oct 6, 1984: Western football and Glen Worthy "Mr. Stick."
    - November 1984 Clippings (copies), 55623 (Box clippings_1, Folder 57)
      Nov 3, 1984: Contracts signed for design of field house complex; Nov 6, 1984: Prof.Dennis Kenney rides subways in search of thesis; Nov 14, 1984: Guardian Angel, Lisa Sliwa, speaks at WCSU; Nov 15, 1984: Prof. Ellen Rosenberg and WCSU's Center for Urban Studies; Nov 15, 1984: John Toland and Dr. Roman to lead methods class in history research; Nov 15, 1984: Moliere's Tartuffe by the Communications and Theatre Arts Department; Nov 19,20, 1984: Dr. Walter Bernstein designed superintendent-in-residence program; Nov 23, 1984: Assoc. Prof. Jan Henson Dow chosen one of four finalists for the 1985 National Play Award of $12,500; Nov 24, 1984: WCSU Chaplain Dr. Robert Wolsch.
    - November 1984 Clippings (copies) - Sports, 55622 (Box clippings_1, Folder 58)
      Nov 3, 1984: Running backs Dave Atkinson, Scott Haney and Mike Megura featured; Nov 10, 1984: Football coaching staff growth/staff photograph; Nov 17, 1984: Harry Hyra, traveling basketball consultant; Nov 18, 1984: WestConn men open with hoop victory.
    - December 1984 Clippings (copies), 55621 (Box clippings_1, Folder 59)
      Dec 8,9, 1984: Dallas K. Beal becomes President of CSU; Dec 16, 1984: Prof. Lu, and student Michael Wiggs to study evolution of stars in Chile; Dec 19, 1984: Nathan Ancell's business ethics class; Dec 24, 1984: Few being enticed into teaching despite incentives; Dec 24, 1984: Dr. Mel Goldstein to make movie on maritime meteorology; Dec 30, 1984: Virginia Steinkrauss, wife of Phillip Steinkrauss, interview.
    - December 1984 Clippings (copies) - Sports, 55620 (Box clippings_1, Folder 60)
      Dec 18, 1984: Women's basketball team wins Tip-Off Tournament; Dec 30, 1984: Women's basketball team unbeaten.
  - 1985, 55603
    - January 1985 Clippings (copies), 55618 (Box clippings_1, Folder 61)
      Jan 10, 1985: Francesco Gianninoto interview; Jan 27, 1985: States' leaders to meet in Danbury.
    - February 1985 Clippings (copies), 55617 (Box clippings_1, Folder 62)
      Feb 10, 1985: Boehringer Ingelheim revamps organization; Feb 21, 1985: Prof. Dennis Kenney's survey on subway crime; Feb 27, 1985: Economists George Gilder and Martin Felstein debate; Feb 28, 1985: Severe storm conference and Dr. Mel Goldstein's experimental weather predictor.
    - March 1985 Clippings (copies), 55616 (Box clippings_1, Folder 63)
      Mar 1, 1985: Dr. Mel Goldstein and experimental weather predictor a hit; Mar 3, 1985: WCSU expands law curricula; Mar 21, 1985: Peter Came, historian of Danbury, England, to give annual Gino Arconti Lecture.
    - March 1985 Clippings (copies) - Sports, 55615 (Box clippings_1, Folder 64)
      Mar 15, 1985: Jody Rajacula named Coach of the Year by the New England Women's Basketball Assn.
    - April 1985 Clippings (copies), 55614 (Box clippings_1, Folder 65)
      Apr 19, 1985: WCSU still needs teaching certification by state; Apr 25, 1985: Parking lot funding anticipated; Apr 26, 1985: Dr. Phillip Lu and school's new 16 inch reflector telescope; Apr 29, 1985: Alvin P. Dobsevate interview.
    - May 1985 Clippings (copies), 55613 (Box clippings_1, Folder 66)
      May 10, 1985: Rhys Caparn donates four of her works to WCSU; May 25, 1985: Prof. Eli P.Schutts may sue state.
    - June 1985 Clippings (copies), 55612 (Box clippings_1, Folder 67)
      Jun 20, 1985: Enrollment decline forecast for state colleges; Jun 30, 1985: Dr. Mel Goldstein and his DAX system for predicting severe weather.
    - July 1985 Clippings (copies), 55611 (Box clippings_1, Folder 68)
      Jul 9, 1985: WCSU plans biochemistsry lab; Jul 19, 1985: Dr. Janick and the Historic American Building Survey (HABS); Ju.19, 1985: Boehring Ingelheim gives $100,000 endowment to establish biochemistry lab; Jul 21, 1985: Biologist Peter Siver and Golden Algae (Chrysophyceae); Jul 31, 1985: Constantine Kalogeras interview.
    - August 1985 Clippings (copies), 55610 (Box clippings_1, Folder 69)
      Aug 22, 1985: Leah Ortiz and drama professor Richard Reimold.
    - September 1985 Clippings (copies), 55609 (Box clippings_1, Folder 70)
      Sep 9, 1985: Prof. Alex Westfried studies the issues of feminism in Brazil; Sep 11, 1985: Proposed tuition hike of 10.8%; Sep 26,28-29, 1985: Dr. Mel Goldstein tracking hurricane Gloria.
    - October 1985 Clippings (copies), 55608 (Box clippings_1, Folder 71)
      Oct 2, 1985: Nathan Ancell hosts reception for WCSU's Economics Club and new journal Western's Economic Journal; Oct 9, 1985: Samuel Young obituary (established the Robert S. Young Business Library); Oct 10, 1985: Alexander M. Haig, Jr., speaker, Union Carbide Cororation Lecture Series; Oct 19, 1985: Rabbi Jerome R. Malino marks 50 years in Danbury.
    - November 1985 Clippings (copies), 55607 (Box clippings_1, Folder 72)
      November, 1985: Dr. Mel Goldstein interview; Nov 8, 1985: Economist Irving Kellner spoke at WestConn's 100 Society lunch; Nov 10, 1985: Stephen Feldman's co-authored book Smater Money; Nov 22, 1985: Dr. Phillip Lu and WCSU's new 16-inch reflector telescope.
    - November 1985 Clippings (copies) - Sports, 55606 (Box clippings_1, Folder 73)
      Nov 27, 1985: WCSU drops out of NEFC.
    - December 1985 Clippings (copies), 55605 (Box clippings_1, Folder 74)
      Dec 17, 1985: Future teachers don't do too well on new skill tests; Dec 19, 1985: Ellen and Jamie Prunty interview; "Dec 29, 1985: WCSU becoming more selective in accepted students; Dec 30, 1985: Joan Apple Leomoine becomes dean of Student Affairs.
    - December 1985 Clippings (copies) - Sports, 55604 (Box clippings_1, Folder 75)
      Dec 28, 1985: WCSU basketball team departs for Europe on 11 day, four game tour.
  - 1986, 55590
    - January 1986 Clippings (copies), 55602 (Box clippings_1, Folder 76)
      Jan 3,6,8, 1986: Rhys Caparn donates sculptures to WCSU; n.d., 1986: Plonia Nixon (artist) Interview.
    - February 1986 Clippings (copies), 55601 (Box clippings_1, Folder 77)
      Feb 4,24, 1986: $45,000 grant to WCSU from Adolph Coors Company and the A. Gallo Distributing Company; Feb 11, 1986: WestConn weather crew will establish formal fee for services; Feb 20, 1986: Del Kinney interview; Feb 20, 1986: WCSU receives state accreditation for new B.A. in Computer Science; Feb 28, 1986: Pippin by the Communications and Theatre Arts Department
    - March 1986 Clippings (copies), 55600 (Box clippings_1, Folder 78)
      Mar 11, 1986: Kathleen Rosenthal and Kenneth Fricker, Charles Ives Center; Mar 14, 1986: The Hartford Courant and Dr. Mel Goldstein; Mar 18,21, 1986: Martin Luther King III to speak in Danbury; Mar 21, 1986: Joan Apple Lemoine, new dean of Student Affairs.
    - April 1986 Clippings (copies), 55599 (Box clippings_1, Folder 79)
      Apr 4, 1986: Justice students will investigate activities of the KKK and other white supremacist organizations in Montgomery, Alabama; Apr 14, 1986: Harold Schramm spoke about Thomas Jefferson's influence on church, state; Apr 22, 1986: West Conn's playwrights in the spotlight; Apr 23,26, 1986: Business degree and competing interests.
    - May 1986 Clippings (copies), 55598 (Box clippings_1, Folder 80)
      May 1, 1986: WestConn drama "Anne and Duley" by Raymond Pape wins preliminaries; May 21, 1986: WestConn told to incrase enrollment of minorities; May 25, 1986: Co-op education.
    - June 1986 Clippings (copies), 55597 (Box clippings_1, Folder 81)
      Jun 5, 1986: Teacher prep plan wins approval from State Board of Education; Jun 8, 1986: MBA degree divides universities (WestConn/Uconn); Jun 24, 1986: Bio-chemistry Lab dedication (Boehringer-Ingleheim).
    - July 1986 Clippings (copies), 55596 (Box clippings_1, Folder 82)
      Jul 1, 1986: Bart Henderson designed device to link the campus and weather station computers; Jul 25, 1986: Eric Lewis/Manhattan String Quartet and travel to Russia; Jul 27, 1986: WCSU summer program to update teachers on bio-technology trends; Jul 28, 1986: WCSU's Economic Club and Western's Economic Journal; Jul 29, 1986: Prof. Barbara Winder's poem "The Idea of Peacocks in Hartford."
    - August 1986 Clippings (copies), 55595 (Box clippings_1, Folder 83)
      Aug, 1986: Greater Danbury Business Digest cover story "The Ancell School of Business: Education for the real world of business;" Aug 10, 1986: Walter Bernstein, Dean of Professional Studies, interview; Aug 10, 1986: Frank Dye gives birth to museum of embryology; Aug 31, 1986: Biology professor Peter Siver's discoveries of golden algae.
    - September 1986 Clippings (copies), 55594 (Box clippings_1, Folder 84)
      Sep 7, 1986: Nurses study Soviet Rx for health; Sep 17, 1986: Budget boosts spending for WestConn.
    - October 1986 Clippings (copies), 55593 (Box clippings_1, Folder 85)
      Oct 1, 1986: Shanty that WCSU students built decries apartheid, apathy; Oct 2, 1986: "Designated driver" campaign; Oct 7, 1986: South African Dumisani S. Kumalo speaks at WestConn; Oct 19, 1986: Manhattan String Quartet on second tour of theSoviet Union through Oct 30.
    - November 1986 Clippings (copies), 55592 (Box clippings_1, Folder 86)
      Nov 6,9, 1986: Carbide land sale imminent; Nov 11, 1986: Economic Club offers students free legal referral service; Nov 13, 1986: Barbara Winder's prize winning poems; Nov 14, 1986: Dr. Walter Bernstein: Educators set agenda for 21st century child; Nov 22, 1986: WestConn gets ok on MBA; Nov 25, 1986: WestConn profs. John Leopold and Eric Roman confer before mock tribunal at Danbury High.
    - December 1986 Clippings (copies), 55591 (Box clippings_1, Folder 86)
      Dec 1,3, 1986: Peter Siver and Timothy Simpkins: Lake Candlewood and algae; Dec 8, 1986: Uconn MBA head, Norman E. Puffett, to join WestConn; "Dec 11, 1986: Eric Roman, speaks at seminar for history teachers at New Milford High School.
  - 1987, 55575
    - January 1987 Clippings (copies), 55589 (Box clippings_1, Folder 87)
      Jan 18, 1987: News-Times Community Forum by Walter B. Bernstein: New life pumped into teacher training.
    - February 1987 Clippings (copies), 55588 (Box clippings_1, Folder 88)
      Feb 5, 1987: WestConn, training school targeted for funds; Feb 5, 1987: Julian Bond at press conference; Feb 8, 1987: New York Times: Dr. Mel Goldstein profiled; Feb 26, 1987: Antigone by the Communications and Theatre Arts Department.
    - March 1987 Clippings (copies), 55587 (Box clippings_1, Folder 89)
      Mar 1, 1987: Antigone by the Communications and Theatre Arts Department; Mar 8, 1987: "Meet Dr. Mel;" Mar 13, 1987: News-Times Community Forum by James Pegolotti: "Not academic ability alone that results in student failure;" Mar 13, 1987: Union Carbide Corporation Lecture Series: Henry Kissinger; Mar 17, 1987: New-Times Community Forum by Charles P. Mullaney: "Like Gaul, Northern Ireland situation divided in three parts;" Mar 17, 1987: Dr. Edward Hagan's new book on Irish literature; Mar 31, 1987: WestConn College Bowl team prepares for finals.
    - April 1987 Clippings (copies), 55586 (Box clippings_1, Folder 90)
      Apr 3, 1987: Union Carbide Corporation Lecture Series: WestConn student Greg Brooks to sit on panel when Henry Kissenger speaks; Apr 4, 1987: Review of Henry Kissinger lecture; Apr 27, 1987: Day-care center proposed to aid WestConn students; Apr 29, 1987: Gino Arconti Lecture Series: George Nader review.
    - May 1987 Clippings (copies), 55585 (Box clippings_1, Folder 91)
      May 19: WestConn hosts lecture on Malcolm X by Gil Noble, WABC-TV news correspondent.
    - June 1987 Clippings (copies), 55584 (Box clippings_1, Folder 92)
      Jun 4, 1987: Ronald W. Shaw appointed assistant Vice President for Public Safety and Property Management.
    - July 1987 Clippings (copies), 55583 (Box clippings_1, Folder 93)
      Jul 15, 1987: WestConn to open child care center; Jul 21, 1987: WestConn hires Kenneth P. Healy as first Alumni Director; Jul 24, 1987: Union Carbide donates a collection of business related books and periodicals to Young Library; Jul 25-26, 1987: Carol A. Hawkes becomes Dean of the School of Arts and Sciences; Jul 29, 1987: WestConn to start offering MBA program this fall.
    - August 1987 Clippings (copies), 55582 (Box clippings_1, Folder 94)
      August, 1987: Greater Danbury Business Digest: Dean Neil Wagner and Dr. Norman Puffett; Union Carbide, and Unimation; Aug 21, 1987: WestConn names H. Richard Dozier Associate Dean; Aug 29, 1987: Constantine Kalogeras resigns as dean of Ancell School of Business.
    - August 1987 Clippings (copies) - Sports, 55581 (Box clippings_1, Folder 95)
      Aug 20, 1987: WestConn names Chris Rippon football coach.
    - September 1987 Clippings (copies), 55580 (Box clippings_1, Folder 96)
      Sep 1, 1987: Albert C. Stewart named acting Dean of Ancell School of Business; Sep 24, 1987: IBM manager W. Jason Hancock working at WestConn under the IBM Faculty Loan Program.
    - October 1987 Clippings (copies), 55579 (Box clippings_1, Folder 97)
      Oct 26, 1987: Prof. Alex Westfried interview; Oct 31, 1987: Feldman and faculty to meet.
    - October 1987 Clippings (copies) - Sports, 55578 (Box clippings_1, Folder 98)
      Oct 16, 1987: Student John Fillyaw profiled.
    - November 1987 Clippings (copies), 55577 (Box clippings_1, Folder 99)
      Nov 1, 1987: Carol Hawkes interview; Nov 3,19,24,29, 1987: WestConn faculty and Feldman discuss strained relations; Nov 9,15, 1987: Susan L. Taylor, Essence editor, speaks to minority youth at Ancell; Nov 18, 1987: Unique minority scholarship program set at WestConn.
    - December 1987 Clippings (copies), 55576 (Box clippings_1, Folder 100)
      Dec 1,6, 1987: Dr. Lu to study black holes in Chile; Dec 6, 1987: Connecticut libraries' collections lagging; Dec 9,15, 1987: Feldman and faculty discussions.
  - 1988, 55561
    - January 1988 Clippings (copies), 55574 (Box clippings_1, Folder 101)
      Jan 21,28,31, 1988: WestConn discontent and peace proposals.
    - February 1988 Clippings (copies), 55573 (Box clippings_1, Folder 102)
      Feb 7, 1988: Gov. O'Neill proposes $8.3 million improvement program for WestConn; Feb 10, 1988: Cicely Tyson speaks at WestConn; Feb 14, 1988: Basic Studies Program; Feb 18,20, 1988: WestConn teachers seek representative to solve communication problems with Feldman; Feb 26, 1988: "The Follies of '45" co-authored by Prof. Jan Henson Dow; Feb 28, 1988: Dr. Mel Goldstein and forecasting weather; Feb 29, 1988: Dr. Lu wins grant to study farthest edges of the Milky Way.
    - March 1988 Clippings (copies), 55572 (Box clippings_1, Folder 103)
      Mar 3, 1988: WestConn Foundation disclosure limited; Mar 10, 1988: Prof. Robert J. Merrer uses software gift from Beckman Instruments, Inc.; Mar 13, 1988: Prof. Karen Jambeck retells the fables of Marie de France, a medieval author.
    - April 1988 Clippings (copies), 55571 (Box clippings_1, Folder 104)
      Apr 4, 1988: Guys and Dolls by the Communications and Theatre Arts Department; Apr 4,21, 1988: Union Carbide Lecture Series: Louis Rukeyser to speak on nation's economy; Apr 8, 1988: Prof. Howard Russock is new faculty ombudsman; Apr 10,12,19, 1988: WestConn Foundation has $1.5 million at its disposal; Apr 12,21, 1988: WestConn police videotaped SGA sponsored studenty rally; Apr 12,19-20, 1988: Rally urges tenure for Saul Mekies; Apr 27, 1988: Dr. Mel Goldstein testifies about weather conditions at Richard Crafts' murder trial.
    - May 1988 Clippings (copies), 55570 (Box clippings_1, Folder 105)
      May 4, 1988: Jim Pegolotti profile in The Bethel Home News; May 5, 1988: Stephen Feldman and faculty discontent; May 5-6,11-14, 1988: Bob Keeshan "Captain Kangaroo" to be graduation speaker; May 5,16, 1988: Letter to Editor: Student defends teacher (Saul Mekies); May 12, 1988: WestConn student wins FOI decision against Foundation (Saul Mekies); May 15, 1988: News-Times Community Forum by Peter A. Lyons "WestConn needs and administrator."
    - June 1988 Clippings (copies), 55569 (Box clippings_1, Folder 106)
      Jun 16,18, 1988: Dr. Philip Lu invited to lecture in the People's Republic of China; Jun 26, 1988: Foundation opens audit report on finances.
    - July 1988 Clippings (copies), 55568 (Box clippings_1, Folder 107)
      Jul 10, 1988: Albert C. Stewart, interim Ancell dean; Jul 13, 1988: State budget crunch at WestConn; Jul 14, 1988: Peter Siver continues research into acid rain; Jul 15, 1988: State rejects audit request on WestConn; Jul 17,22, 1988: WestConn's MBA program; Jul 24, 1988: Steps-Up program for freshmen in need of remedial help.
    - August 1988 Clippings (copies), 55567 (Box clippings_1, Folder 108)
      Aug 7, 1988: WestConn's receives approval from CSUS for B.A. in meteorology; Aug 9, 1988: Open school foundation, say legislature auditors.
    - September 1988 Clippings (copies), 55566 (Box clippings_1, Folder 109)
      Sep 7, 1988: Feldman addresses faculty; Sep 15,16,18,29, 1988: AAUP meet to decide what action to take against Stephen Feldman; Sep 23, 1988: WestConn dissent continues with two new underground newspapers; Sep 28, 1988: WestConn win $6M to build field house and $7.2M for addition on Haas Library, and $1.6M for residence hall on westside campus.
    - October 1988 Clippings (copies), 55565 (Box clippings_1, Folder 110)
      Oct 1,8, 1988: FOI and WestConn Foundation; Oct 2,4,, 1988: Feldman interview re controversy, petition; Oct 9, 1988: Child care program ends at WestConn; Oct 14, 1988: Streamers by the Communications and Theatre Arts Department; Oct 20,27-29, 1988: Faculty vs. Feldman and Dean of Personnel Frank Muska.
    - November 1988 Clippings (copies), 55564 (Box clippings_1, Folder 111)
      Nov 4,15,17-18, 1988: Faculty vote on Feldman this month; Nov 7, 1988: The Odd Couple production by the Communications and Theatre Arts Department; Nov 13, 1988: Racial balance sought on campus; Nov 23, 1988: Faculty declined opportunity to voice complaints to Boards of Trustees; Nov 29, 1988: Carbide gives $20,000 for lecture series.
    - December 1988 Clippings (copies), 55563 (Box clippings_1, Folder 112)
      Dec 2-3,9, 1988: Faculty vs. Feldman; Dec 14,20, 1988: WestConn Foundation agrees to audit; Dec 20,22, 1988: Faculty vs. Feldman: State probe fails to solve WestConn dispute.
    - December 1988 Clippings (copies) - Sports, 55562 (Box clippings_1, Folder 113)
      December, 1988: Men's and women's basketball and soccer; Dec 15, 1988: Ron Gleissner receives academic honor.
  - 1989, 55542
    - January 1989 Clippings (copies), 55560 (Box clippings_1, Folder 114)
      January 1989: Greater Danbury Business Digest: Greater Danbury's quality of life is tops (WestConn, Donald and Pat Weeden, and Dr. Mel Goldstein profiled; Jan 1, 1989: Area's top ten stories in 1988: No.10 WCSU and Stephen Feldman; Jan 4,10,19,30, 1989: WestConn Foundation and auditors; Jan 8,18,24, 1989: Dr. Mel Goldstein interview and B.A. in Meteorology; Jan 8, 1989: Dr. Lyn Christie interview; Jan 20,24,26, 1989: Faculty vs. Feldman and Muska; Jan 29, 1989: John Briggs interview.
    - January 1989 Clippings (copies) - Sports, 55559 (Box clippings_1, Folder 115)
      Jan 4, 1989: Men's basketball.
    - February 1989 Clippings (copies), 55558 (Box clippings_1, Folder 116)